{
    "id": "b6b450999e9b42e69495824ddb1dc22b",
    "title": "Sequence of tenses quiz",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "125b89de52734a5f91a81dd0a52b6615",
            "title": "Sequence Of Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You will find Coca-Cola wherever you ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "went",
                        "would go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He would never do anything that ………………… .. against his conscience.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "goes",
                        "went",
                        "will go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will lend it to you on condition that you ……………………… it back tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bring",
                        "would bring",
                        "brought"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… a good time whether I win or lose.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "had",
                        "will have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "One day the government will ask people what they ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "want",
                        "will want",
                        "wanted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know where she …………………. tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "will be",
                        "would be"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had lots of money, I would give some to anybody who ………………… for it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ask",
                        "asks",
                        "asked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have brought my tennis things, just in case we ………………… time for a game tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "will have",
                        "would have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will go where you …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "will go",
                        "would go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will tell you when I …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finished",
                        "have finished",
                        "had finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}